<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<Note start_block="14" end_block="20">
  <paragraph block_index="14">1. NATURE OF OPERATIONS AND GOING CONCERN</paragraph>
  <paragraph block_index="15">BestCo Ltd. (formerly GoodCo Ltd.) (the “Company”) was incorporated pursuant to the Business Corporations Act of British Columbia on January 24, 2011. The Company’s registered office is located at 13th Floor, 1313 Lucky Street, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, V1C 2D3. The Company is listed for trading on the TSX Venture Exchange under the symbol “BCL”.</paragraph>
  <paragraph block_index="16">The Company is engaged in the operation, acquisition, exploration and development of mineral properties in Latin America, with a primary focus on silver and zinc, including lead and copper. As at December 31, 2023, the Company haone producing project, the Great Mine. The Company has acquired, or has options to acquire, the mining concession rights to the following properties:</paragraph>
  <paragraph block_index="17">The producing Great Mine located in Mexico</paragraph>
  <paragraph block_index="18">Various other properties in San Luis Potosi, Mexico, noting that the Rocket Project had been placed on care and maintenance in August 2023 (Note 6).</paragraph>
  <paragraph block_index="19">These consolidated financial statements for the years ended December 31, 2023 and 2022 (“financial statements”) have been prepared on a going concern basis, which assumes that the Company will be able to meet its obligations and continue its operations for at least the next twelve months. As at December 31, 2023, the Company has a working capital deficiency of $19,821 (December 31, 2022 - $22,514) and an accumulated deficit of $137,942 (December 31, 2022 - $126,377). Additionally, the Company has non-current loans payable (Note 14) of $7,166 (December 31, 2022 - $nil). For the year ended December 31, 2023, the Company incurred a loss of $11,459 (2022 - $1,116) and used cash in operating activities of $1,472 (2022 - $4,811). These factors indicate the existence of a material uncertainty that may cast significant doubt upon the Company’s ability to continue as a going concern. As a result, the Company may be unable to realize its assets and discharge its liabilities in the normal course of business. The Company’s ability to continue as a going concern is dependent upon its ability to generate positive cash flows from operations, and/or raise adequate funding through equity or debt financing to discharge its liabilities as they come due. Although the Company has been successful in the past in obtaining financing, there is no assurance that it will be able to obtain adequate financing in the future or that such financing will be on terms advantageous to the Company.</paragraph></Note>
